Guide to the Pennsylvania State University, Department of Animal Nutrition records 00044
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- Experiments and Projects, 4
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 5 - Low Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 7 - Low Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 8 - High Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 10 - High Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 11 - Low Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 12 - High Protein, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 1 - The Ventilation, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Air Analysis, 1953-1954 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 1 Low Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 8 Low Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment1160 - Per. 3 High Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 5 High Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 7 Low Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 6 High Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 4 High Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 2 Low Fat, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 7 - 12 Light Breakfast, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 1 - 6 Regular Breakfast, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Blank and CO2 Recovery, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 1160 - Per. 1 - 8 Ventilation, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Experiment 248 - Cow 1 - Periods 1-16, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Experiment 248 - Cows 4-12 - Periods 1-16, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Experiment 248 - Balances of Nitrogen and Mineral Elements (Cows 1-12), undated (Box 16)
  - Experiment 248 - Dry Matter of Hay and Grain Eaten, undated (Box 16)
  - Experiment 248 - Balances - Cows 1-12, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Relation Among the Constituents of Milk, undated (Box 16)
  - Experiment 1056, 1946 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Balance of Matter and Energy - Digestion Coefficients/Urine Values, 1946-47 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Analytical Sheets - feces samples, undated (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 1-5, December 1946 - January 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 6-11, January - February 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 13-14, 16-20, 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 21-28, May-June 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 1-11 - Ventilation, December 1946 - February 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 13-14, 16-20 - Ventilation, February-April 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Periods 21-28 - Ventilation, May-June 1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 1056 - Tube Weights (Log Book), 1946-1947 (Box 18)
  - Experiment 200 - Utilization of Feed, 1906 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 207 - Influence of Age and Individuality on the Matabolism of Steers, 1907 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 208 - Heat Study, undated (Box 21)
  - Experiment 209 - Feeding Log, 1907-1909 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 210 - Energy Values of Corn Stover, 1908-1909 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 211 - Energy Values of Mixt Clover, Tim Hay, Cornmeal and Hominy Feed, 1909-1910 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Periods I - VI - Steer H, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Periods I - VI - Ventilation, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Samples - Periods 1-5, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Periods I-VI - Residual CO2 Samples, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Averaging Mercury Thermometer Readings, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Alfalfa Hay and Meal Tables, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Tables, 1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 212 - Notebook, 1911-1912 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 216 - Computations, undated (Box 21)
  - Experiment 217 - Influence of Condition Upon the Metabolism of Cattle, 1913-1914 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 220 - Net Energy Values of Red Clover Hay and Maize Meal, 1914-1915 (Box 21)
  - Experiment 935 B - Preliminary Tables (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B -Daily Record of Feed, Live Weight and Excreta, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B and C - Computation of Digestibility, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Daily Record of Carbon Loss on Drying of Silage, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1 - 5 (Steer 14), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1, 2 and 4 (Steer 15), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1 - 5 (Steer 16), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1-3 (Steer 14-16), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1 -5 - Ventilation (Steer 14), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Periods 1 -5 - Ventilation (Steer 16), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Ingest and Outcome - H2O Temp. - Periods 1 and 2 (Steer 14 and 16), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Water Temp. Differences - Periods 3-5 (Steer 14 and 16), 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Final Tables, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 935 B - Analytical Results, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
  - Experiment 240 - Periods 1-13, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Periods 14 and 15 - Fasting, 1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Periods 1-15 - Analytical Results and Data, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Periods 1-15 - Ventilation, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Heat Measurements, undated (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Tables, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Hide Areas, 1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Daily Records: Feed/Weight/Water, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Fasting Tables (Sets 1 and 2), 1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 240 - Log Books - Steer #60, 1927-1928 (Box 24)
  - Experiment 236 - Iron in Meats, 1924-1925 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Insensible Perspiration, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Tables Set 1, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Fasting Experiments - Periods 6 and 7, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Absorber Capacity, 1926 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Data and Records, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Steer 36, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Steer 47, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 1 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1926 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 2a Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1926 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 2 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1926 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 3 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 4 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 5 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 6 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 7 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 8 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 9 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 10 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 11 Steer 47 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 Per. 12 Steer 36 - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Manuscript, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 - Ventilation Log Book, 1926-1927 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 238 and 240 - Correction of Live Weight, 1941 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 A - Utilization of Iron in Meats by Rats, 1927-1928 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 A - Iron Contents in Rats, Fed a Stock Diet, 1928 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 A - Publications, 1929 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 A - A Method for Determining a small Amount of Iron, 1930 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 A - Copper, Manganese and Zinc in Rat Rations, 1929 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 B - Literature, 1927-1929 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 B -New Work - Notes, 1929-1930 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 B - References (Iron and Meat), 1930 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 239 B - Completed Records - Summaries, 1929-1931 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 240 - Insensible Perspiration, undated (Box 28)
  - Experiment 249 - Periods 1 and 2 - Cow (Grace), 1931 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 249 - Ventilation, 1931 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 249 - Heat Production and the Rate of Ventilation, 1931 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 249 - Analysis, 1931 (Box 28)
  - Experiment 871 E - Blanks and Preliminary Tests, 1941-1942 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 E - Periods 1-7, Champbers 1 and 2), 1942 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 E - Respiration Bottles 1-4, 1943 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 G - Preliminary Feeding of Rat Diet to Best Eaters, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 G and H - Weight Equivalents of Rations, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 H - Rat Study, 1944 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 I - Rat Diet Study, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 I - Respiration Chambers 1 and 2, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 J - Respiration Chamber 1, 1946 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 J, K and L - Haldane Mature Rats - Body Balance - Copper Cage, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 L - Daily CO2 Production, 1946 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 L - Results of Analysis, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 M - Low Protein Diet, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 N - Heat Production, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 N - CO2 Measurements (Low Fat Diet), 1947 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 N - Record of CO2 Measurements, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 N, O, P and Q - Negatives of Charts, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 P - Cages 1-3, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 Q - Cage 1, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 R - Heat Increments and Feed, 1947 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 R - Groups 1-3, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 V - Rats and Amino Acids, 1951 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 V - Nitrogen and Energy Metabolism, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 V - Standard Errors and Probabilities, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 V - Body Balance Tables, undated (Box 31)
  - Experiment 871 V - Nitrogen and Energy Metabolism of Proteins and Amino Acids, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Experiment 872 A - Preliminary Tables, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Air Analysis, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Fasting Tables, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Final Tables, 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Temperature Averages (Periods 1-4, Steer 44), 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Temperature Averages (Periods 2-4, Steer 55), 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Temperature Averages (Periods 1-4, Steer 66), 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Ventilation - Periods 1-4, Steer 44, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Ventilation - Periods 2-4, Steer 55, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Ventilation - Periods 1-4, Steer 66, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Periods 1-4, Steer 44, 1939-1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Periods 1-4, Steer 55, 1939-1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Periods 1-4, Steer 66, 1939-1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Analytical Results, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 A - Daily Records of Live Weight, Feed and Excreta, 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 B - Group 1 Rats (Periods 1-3), 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 B - Group 4 Rats (Periods 1-3), 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 B - Rat Study, 1939-1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 B - Rats and Dog Chow Rations, 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 C - Rat Study, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 C - Rats (Group 1), 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 C - Group 1 Rats (Periods 1-3), 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 872 C - Group 2 Rats (Periods 1-3), 1940 (Box 32)
  - Experiment 261 - Record of Feed, Live Weight and Water, 1931 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Air Analysis, 1931 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Thermometer Readings for Heat Computation, 1931 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Institute of Animal Nutrition, 1931-1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Analytical Data, 1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Heat Production/Sprometer Samples (all Periods) (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Effects of Feeds on Feed Energy (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Preliminary Tables (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Tables (Sets 1 and 2) (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Periods 1,3,5,7,9 and 11 (Steer A), 1931-1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Periods 2,4,6,8,10,12 and 14 (Steer B), 1931-1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Ventilation - Periods 1,3,5,7,9,11 and 13 - (Steer A), 1931-1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 261 - Ventilation - Periods 2,4,6,8,10,12 and 14 - (Steer B), 1931-1932 (Box 33)
  - Experiment 933 - Log Books I and II, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 934 - Rabbits (1 - 40), 1938 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 934 - Digestible Nutrients for the Domestic Rabbit, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 934 - Rabbits and Various Feeds, 1938 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 934 - Log Book (Deer and Rabbits), 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 934 - Deer Project, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 -Heat Production of Rats, 1937 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 - Periods 1-4 - Analytical Sheets, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 - Periods 5-8 - Analytical Data, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 - Digestibility Tables, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 - Live Weight/Feed/Excreta, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 A - Rations 1 and 5, 1937 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 935 B - Alfalfa and Alfalfa Silage, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 - Heat Measurements, 1938-1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 - Respiratory Quotients, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 A - Rat Study - CO2 and H2O, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 B - Air Bath, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 B - Ventilation and Heat Production, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 B and C - Critical Temperature, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 C - Critical Temperature of Young Rats, 1940 (Box 34)
  - Preliminary Work on Critical Temperature of Guinea Pigs, 1942 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 D - Tables, 1943 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 D - Albino Rats, 1943 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 D - Original Data Sheets, 1943-1944 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 936 D - Effect of Feed, Critical Temp. and the Albino Rat, 1944 (Box 34)
  - Experiment 857 - Phosphorous Deficiency, undated (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 S - Log Book, 1937 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 S - Plane of Protein Intake by C-N Balance, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 - Log Book, 1941 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 V - Chloride (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 W - Chloride Deficiency (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 W - Chloride Deficiency - Statistical Data (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 W - Chloride Deficiency - Analytical Results and Tables (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 W - Chloride Deficiency (Log Book) (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 - Ca and Fat Utilization (Log Book), 1941 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 X - Calcium and Fat Utilization (1st and 2nd exp.), 1941 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 X - Fat and Calcium Absorbtion, 1941 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 857 Z - Thiamin and the Metabolism of Carbohydrates, Protein and Fat, 1941-1942 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 864 Periods 1 and 2 (Cows and Sheep), 1934 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 864 Periods 3 and 4 (Cows and Sheep), 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Dynamic Effects of Proteins, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Dynamic Effects of Casein, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Metabolism of Amino Acids (Log Book), 1940 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - SDE of Amino Acids (Log Book), 1939 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Balances of Matter and Energy, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Basal Daily and the Effects of Proteins, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Progress Reports, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 865 - Effect of Casein, Gelatin and Meat, 1934 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 1019 - Analytical Data, 1944 (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Chemical Composition of Samples, 1943 (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 -Forestry Building Plots (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Nutrition Investigation, 1944-1945 (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - First Draft of Paper, 1947 (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - First Draft of Abstract, 1948 (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Literature References (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Moisture) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Crude Fiber) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Nitrogen) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Energy) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Ether Extract) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Calcium) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Phosphorous) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Magnesium) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (Potassium) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 1019 - Computations - Bluegrass and Clover (K1, K2, K3, K4) (Box 36)
  - Experiment 865 - Summary and Conclusions, 1936 (Box 35)
  - Experiment 875 - 1st and 2nd Experiments, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Notes, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Charts and Notes, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Dog Chow, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Tube Weights, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Results of Analysis (Rations 1-3, 5), 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Ration 1 - Periods 1-7, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Rations 2-4, 6 - Live Weight and Feed Consumed, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Ration 3 - Periods 1-5, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - CO2 Measurements - (Rations 1-6), 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - CO2 Measurements - (Rations 1A and 5A), 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Computation of Rations (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Net Energy Computations (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Preliminary Tests - (Soda and Lime Tests), 1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Periods 1 and 4 (Ration 5), 1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Rations 1A and 5A (Live Weight and Feed), 1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Measuring the Efficiency of Diets, 1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 875 - Log Book ( Study of metabolism of Rats by the carbon-nitrogen balance method), 1936-1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 A - Preliminary Data, 1935 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 A - Notebook 1 of 2, 1935 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 A - Notebook 2 of 2, 1935 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 - Digestibility and Balances of Nitrogen, 1935 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 B - Beef - Muscle - Protein, 1936 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 B - Notebook, 1937 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 C and D - Basal Diet, 1938 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 C - Notebook, 1938 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 D - Notebook, 1938 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 S - Daily Records of Feed, 1939 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 S - Tables, 1939 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 871 S - The Influence of Low Levels of Protein on Heat Production (a draft), 1939 (Box 38)
  - Experiment 248, undated (Box 59)
  - Experiment 935 B, undated (Box 59)
  - Experiment 871, undated (Box 59)
  - Experiment 237, undated (Box 59)
  - Experiment 1033, undated (Box 59)
  - Experiment 1016 - Lignin-Crampton Procedure, undated (Box 58)
  - Experiment 871 H - Temperature Charts, 1944 (Box 58)
  - Experiment 248 - Temperature Charts, 1929 (Box 58)
  - Experiment 260 - Fasting, 1932 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 260 - Fasting Tables, 1933 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 260 - Plane of Nutrition, 1931-1932 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 260 - Specific Action of Pure Nutrients, 1932-1933 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 260 - Final Tables, 1933 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 865 S.D.E - (Notebook) - Daily Record, 1934 and 1936 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 865 S.D.E - (Notebook) - Respiration, 1934 and 1936 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 865 S.D.E - (Notebook) - Preparation of Beef Heart, 1937 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 865 S.D.E - (Notebook) - Amino Acids - Glutamic Acid and Glycine, 1937 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 865 S.D.E - (Notebook) - Amino Acids, 1938 (Box 55)
  - Project 935 A and C - Digestion Experiment, 1938 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Crude Fiber, Lignin and Celluloe, 1944 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Variations in Determinations of Digestive Capacity of Sheep, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - TDN Tables, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Lignin in Feces, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period I - Feces, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Computation of Methane Produced, 1940 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Digestibility of Various Feeds, 1944 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1016 - Final Tables, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1033 - Analytical Sheets, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1033 - Feed and Excreta Analysis, undated (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1033 -Sheep, 1945-1946 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Blank and Heat from Light Bulbs, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Blank CO2 and H2O, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - CO2 and H2O Recovery Test, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 1 (NE-16), 1955 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Periods 2 and 3 - High Protein, 1955-1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Periods 4 and 5 - Low Protein, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 6 - High Protein, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 13 - Low Protein, 1957 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 14 - High Protein, 1957 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 1160 - Period 15 - Low Protein, 1957 (Box 55)
  - Experiment 935 D - Computation of Digestibility, 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Preliminary Tables, 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Daily Record of Feed, Live Weight and Excreta, 1941-1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 1 -3 (Steer 14), 1941-1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 5-7 (Steer 15), 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 4-7 (Steer 16), 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Period 4 (Steer 18), 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 1 and 2 (Steer 19), 1941 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Silage (Periods 1, 3, 4 and 6), 1941- 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 1-3 - Ventilation (Steer 14), 1941-1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 5-7 - Ventilation (Steer 15), 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 4-7 - Ventilation (Steer 16), 1942 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Periods 1 and 2 - Ventilation (Steer 19), 1941 (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Analytical Data (Box 26)
  - Experiment 935 D - Temperature Averages - Periods 1-6 (Steer 14-16) (Box 26)
  - Experiment 1016 - Analytical Data - Composition of Feed and Excreta, 1950-1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 F - Feed and Water, 1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 F - Tabulations, 1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 F - Treatment and Digestibility Log Book, 1951-1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 T - Digestibility Data/Balance Data, 1951-1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 T - Periods 9 and 10, 1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 1 - Timothy Hay, 1948 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 1 - Alfalfa and Early Time, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 2 - Alfalfa and Orchard, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 3 - Timothy Hay, 1948 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 3 - Silage, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 4 - Timothy Hay, 1950 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 4 and 4-xtra, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 5 - Timothy Hay, 1948 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 5, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 6 - Silage, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 7 - Alfalfa and Early Timothy, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 8 - Timothy (2nd cutting), 1950 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 8 - Alfalfa and Orchard Green, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 9 - BromeGrass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 10 - Bromegrass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 10 - Orchard Grass, 1950 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 11 - Timothy Hay, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 11, 1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 12, 1952 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 12 - Kentucky Bluegrass, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 13 - Kentucky Bluegrass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 13 - Ladino, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 15 - Kentucky Bluegrass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 17 - Orchard Grass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 19 - Orchard Grass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 -Period 21 - Orchard Grass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 -Period 23 - Orchard Grass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 25 - Alfalfa Hay, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 26 - Alfalfa Hay (Ventilation), 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 1016 - Period 27 - Orchard Grass, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Experiment 259 - Correspondence and General Outline, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Experiment 259 A - Analytical Sheets, 1932 (Box 19)